<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Future Events on Tama-Toledo Community Visioning</title><link>/event/</link><description>Recent content in Future Events on Tama-Toledo Community Visioning</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Steering Committee Meeting</title><link>/event/2022-10-06-meeting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/event/2022-10-06-meeting/</guid><description>There will be NO regular meeting in September.
The original committees from Tama and Toledo, and others who wish to join the effort, are invited to meet and discuss organization, priorities, and next steps.
This meeting will be held in the large meeting room near the back of the Tama Civic Center to avoid potential conflicts with events at the Wieting Theatre.
Agenda specifics: To be announced at a later date.</description></item><item><title>Healthiest State Annual Walk - Tama County</title><link>/event/2022-10-05-healthiest-state-walk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/event/2022-10-05-healthiest-state-walk/</guid><description>Let’s get walking Tama County!
Join us for Iowa Healthiest State 12th Annual Walk.
Together we can help Iowa become the healthiest state in the nation!
This is the only such event that we are aware of in Tama County, so all area residents are welcome and encouraged to attend.</description></item><item><title>Golf Cart Tour - South Tama Rec Trail</title><link>/event/2022-09-28-golf-cart-trail-event/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/event/2022-09-28-golf-cart-trail-event/</guid><description>Ever been interested in discovering the South Tama Rec Trail and learning more about the trail and future plans? Well, on Wednesday, September 28, we will provide a golf cart tour of the South Tama Rec Trail for individuals age 50 and older who cannot comfortably walk the trail. Interested adults may join us between Noon and 3pm at either the Tama Civic Center or Toledo Heights Park for a golf cart ride on the trail.</description></item><item><title>Walking Audit - Tama</title><link>/event/2022-09-15-walking-audit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/event/2022-09-15-walking-audit/</guid><description>Earlier in the year we had a very successful &amp;ldquo;Walking Audit&amp;rdquo; in Toledo. Now it&amp;rsquo;s Tama&amp;rsquo;s turn. On September 15 we have planned a Walking Audit &amp;nbsp; around downtown Tama conducted by an experienced representative from Wellmark&amp;rsquo;s Healthy Hometown &amp;nbsp; initiative.
Previous Next &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Page: / The AARP (American Association of Retired Persons) describes a walking audit as:
&amp;hellip;a simple activity in which an individual or a team observes and evaluates the walkability of a location to document how and if pedestrians can safely travel along a street, navigate an intersection and get from point A to B, C and so on.</description></item></channel></rss>