<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Tama-Toledo Community Visioning</title><link>/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Tama-Toledo Community Visioning</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ribbon Cutting with Photos!</title><link>/2023/07/ribbon-cutting-with-photos/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2023/07/ribbon-cutting-with-photos/</guid><description>What follows is a transcript and photos from our July 14, 2023, ribbon cutting ceremony for the new crosswalks and RRFBs on Business 30 and Broadway in Toledo.
July 14, 2023 – Ribbon Cutting
Today we celebrate Toledo’s first Rectangular Rapid Flashing Beacon. We are so thankful to many of you who have been with us every step of the way. My name is Denise Fletcher a member of the Tama/Toledo Healthy Hometown Committee.</description></item><item><title>Coming Soon to Business 30 and Broadway</title><link>/2023/01/coming-soon-to-business-30-and-broadway/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 11:46:08 -0600</pubDate><guid>/2023/01/coming-soon-to-business-30-and-broadway/</guid><description>Look for this sign as the weather warms up and the city is able to install the rectangular flashing beacon on Business 30 at Broadway in Toledo. We are thankful for all of our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>A Post from Travis Mullen...</title><link>/2022/06/a-post-from-travis-mullen.../</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 18:39:24 -0500</pubDate><guid>/2022/06/a-post-from-travis-mullen.../</guid><description>This shouldn’t have to happen, but in the present there is no other option. This elderly individual is walking in the highway. The highway.
Tama-Toledo Healthy Hometown Committee is working very hard to change this, by making the community more walkable.
Tama and Toledo city leadership: We’ve ignored the need for a continuous sidewalk along highway 63 for decades. Please support the work of the committee to the greatest extent possible and let’s get this done.</description></item><item><title>Welcome!</title><link>/2021/12/welcome/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 13:05:18 -0600</pubDate><guid>/2021/12/welcome/</guid><description>Welcome to the new internet home of Tama-Toledo Community Visioning! Please check out our About &amp;nbsp; page to learn more about the group.
You may also find online resources at the web pages provided by Iowa&amp;rsquo;s Community Visioning organization, specifically the Tama &amp;nbsp; and Toledo &amp;nbsp; pages. However, we found these pages to be difficult to maintain with limited features, so most of what you find there is meant for download only, and eventually we hope to have all of that material here in a more presentable form.</description></item></channel></rss>