<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>General on Tama-Toledo Community Visioning</title><link>/categories/general/</link><description>Recent content in General on Tama-Toledo Community Visioning</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 08:43:21 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Video from the Iowa Living Roadway Conference</title><link>/2023/11/video-from-the-iowa-living-roadway-conference/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 08:43:21 -0500</pubDate><guid>/2023/11/video-from-the-iowa-living-roadway-conference/</guid><description>This video, produced by Jeff Jensen and starring Denise Fletcher, a co-chair of the Tama-Toledo Community Visioning effort, was shown at the 2023 Iowa Living Roadway Conference held in Ames, Iowa, on November 2.</description></item><item><title>RRFB Video</title><link>/education/rrfb-video/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 17:37:55 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/rrfb-video/</guid><description>RRFB (Rectangular Rapid Flashing Beacon) Guide for Pedestrians and Bicycles 2023 will see a new RRFB and crosswalk installed at the corner of Business US 30 and Broadway in Toledo. The installation is intended to dramatically increase safety for the multitude of pedestrians and bicyclists who cross Business 30 at Broadway every day.
The following video may benefit pedestrians and bicycle riders who will use the new crossing.</description></item><item><title>RRFB Guide for Motorists</title><link>/education/rrfb-motorists/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 17:21:36 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/rrfb-motorists/</guid><description>RRFB (Rectangular Rapid Flashing Beacon) Guide for Motorists 2023 will see a new RRFB and crosswalk installed at the corner of Business US 30 and Broadway in Toledo. The installation is intended to dramatically increase safety for the multitude of pedestrians and bicyclists who cross Business 30 at Broadway every day.
The following guide may benefit motorists who approach the new crosswalk along Business 30.</description></item><item><title>RRFB Guide for Pedestrians and Bicycle Riders</title><link>/education/rrfb-pedestrians-and-bicycles/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 17:21:27 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/rrfb-pedestrians-and-bicycles/</guid><description>RRFB (Rectangular Rapid Flashing Beacon) Guide for Pedestrians and Bicycles 2023 will see a new RRFB and crosswalk installed at the corner of Business US 30 and Broadway in Toledo. The installation is intended to dramatically increase safety for the multitude of pedestrians and bicyclists who cross Business 30 at Broadway every day.
The following guide may benefit pedestrians and bicycle riders who will use the new crossing.</description></item><item><title>Coming Soon to Business 30 and Broadway</title><link>/2023/01/coming-soon-to-business-30-and-broadway/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 11:46:08 -0600</pubDate><guid>/2023/01/coming-soon-to-business-30-and-broadway/</guid><description>Look for this sign as the weather warms up and the city is able to install the rectangular flashing beacon on Business 30 at Broadway in Toledo. We are thankful for all of our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>The 5-2-1-0 Program</title><link>/education/5-2-1-0-posts-january-2023-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 09:52:46 -0600</pubDate><guid>/education/5-2-1-0-posts-january-2023-1/</guid><description>5-2-1-0 Healthy Choices Count! Tama/Toledo was awarded a 3-year 5-2-1-0 grant in 2022. 5-2-1-0 Healthy Choices Count! is a public-private partnership that encourages Iowa children and their families to make healthy lifestyle choices using evidence-based healthy eating and active living approaches. This graphic shows the daily recommendations.</description></item><item><title>The 5-2-1-0 Program</title><link>/education/5-2-1-0-posts-january-2023-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 09:52:46 -0600</pubDate><guid>/education/5-2-1-0-posts-january-2023-2/</guid><description>5-2-1-0 Healthy Choices Count! What is Healthy Choices Count! or 5-2-1-0? An initiative through the Iowa Department of Public Health that provides provides communities, teachers, parents, child care providers, health care providers, and business leaders resources to increase physical activity and healthy eating through policy and environmental change. The graphic explains the meaning of 5-2-1-0.</description></item><item><title>A Post from Travis Mullen...</title><link>/2022/06/a-post-from-travis-mullen.../</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 18:39:24 -0500</pubDate><guid>/2022/06/a-post-from-travis-mullen.../</guid><description>This shouldn’t have to happen, but in the present there is no other option. This elderly individual is walking in the highway. The highway.
Tama-Toledo Healthy Hometown Committee is working very hard to change this, by making the community more walkable.
Tama and Toledo city leadership: We’ve ignored the need for a continuous sidewalk along highway 63 for decades. Please support the work of the committee to the greatest extent possible and let’s get this done.</description></item><item><title>Welcome!</title><link>/2021/12/welcome/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 13:05:18 -0600</pubDate><guid>/2021/12/welcome/</guid><description>Welcome to the new internet home of Tama-Toledo Community Visioning! Please check out our About &amp;nbsp; page to learn more about the group.
You may also find online resources at the web pages provided by Iowa&amp;rsquo;s Community Visioning organization, specifically the Tama &amp;nbsp; and Toledo &amp;nbsp; pages. However, we found these pages to be difficult to maintain with limited features, so most of what you find there is meant for download only, and eventually we hope to have all of that material here in a more presentable form.</description></item></channel></rss>