<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Education on Tama-Toledo Community Visioning</title><link>/education/</link><description>Recent content in Education on Tama-Toledo Community Visioning</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 17:37:55 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>RRFB Video</title><link>/education/rrfb-video/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 17:37:55 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/rrfb-video/</guid><description>RRFB (Rectangular Rapid Flashing Beacon) Guide for Pedestrians and Bicycles 2023 will see a new RRFB and crosswalk installed at the corner of Business US 30 and Broadway in Toledo. The installation is intended to dramatically increase safety for the multitude of pedestrians and bicyclists who cross Business 30 at Broadway every day.
The following video may benefit pedestrians and bicycle riders who will use the new crossing.</description></item><item><title>RRFB Guide for Motorists</title><link>/education/rrfb-motorists/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 17:21:36 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/rrfb-motorists/</guid><description>RRFB (Rectangular Rapid Flashing Beacon) Guide for Motorists 2023 will see a new RRFB and crosswalk installed at the corner of Business US 30 and Broadway in Toledo. The installation is intended to dramatically increase safety for the multitude of pedestrians and bicyclists who cross Business 30 at Broadway every day.
The following guide may benefit motorists who approach the new crosswalk along Business 30.</description></item><item><title>RRFB Guide for Pedestrians and Bicycle Riders</title><link>/education/rrfb-pedestrians-and-bicycles/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 17:21:27 -0500</pubDate><guid>/education/rrfb-pedestrians-and-bicycles/</guid><description>RRFB (Rectangular Rapid Flashing Beacon) Guide for Pedestrians and Bicycles 2023 will see a new RRFB and crosswalk installed at the corner of Business US 30 and Broadway in Toledo. The installation is intended to dramatically increase safety for the multitude of pedestrians and bicyclists who cross Business 30 at Broadway every day.
The following guide may benefit pedestrians and bicycle riders who will use the new crossing.</description></item><item><title>The 5-2-1-0 Program</title><link>/education/5-2-1-0-posts-january-2023-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 09:52:46 -0600</pubDate><guid>/education/5-2-1-0-posts-january-2023-1/</guid><description>5-2-1-0 Healthy Choices Count! Tama/Toledo was awarded a 3-year 5-2-1-0 grant in 2022. 5-2-1-0 Healthy Choices Count! is a public-private partnership that encourages Iowa children and their families to make healthy lifestyle choices using evidence-based healthy eating and active living approaches. This graphic shows the daily recommendations.</description></item><item><title>The 5-2-1-0 Program</title><link>/education/5-2-1-0-posts-january-2023-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 09:52:46 -0600</pubDate><guid>/education/5-2-1-0-posts-january-2023-2/</guid><description>5-2-1-0 Healthy Choices Count! What is Healthy Choices Count! or 5-2-1-0? An initiative through the Iowa Department of Public Health that provides provides communities, teachers, parents, child care providers, health care providers, and business leaders resources to increase physical activity and healthy eating through policy and environmental change. The graphic explains the meaning of 5-2-1-0.</description></item></channel></rss>